http://fbgfarms.com/pages/privacy-policy

Search
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.fredericksburgfarms.com and Fredericksburg Farms and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Fredericksburg Farms include www.fredericksburgfarms.com. The Fredericksburg Farms website is a Retail site. By using the Fredericksburg Farms website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Fredericksburg Farms may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:
Name
Address
E-mail Address
Phone Number
If you purchase Fredericksburg Farms products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.
Fredericksburg Farms encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Fredericksburg Farms so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Fredericksburg Farms is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Fredericksburg Farms website.
Use of your Personal Information
Fredericksburg Farms collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
Fredericksburg Farms may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Fredericksburg Farms and its affiliates. Fredericksburg Farms may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Fredericksburg Farms does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Fredericksburg Farms may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Fredericksburg Farms, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Fredericksburg Farms may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Fredericksburg Farms, in order to determine what Fredericksburg Farms services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Fredericksburg Farms to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Fredericksburg Farms will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Fredericksburg Farms or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Fredericksburg Farms; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Fredericksburg Farms, or the public.
Automatically Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Fredericksburg Farms. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Fredericksburg Farms website.
Use of Cookies
The Fredericksburg Farms website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Fredericksburg Farms pages, or register with Fredericksburg Farms site or services, a cookie helps Fredericksburg Farms to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Fredericksburg Farms website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Fredericksburg Farms features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Fredericksburg Farms services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Fredericksburg Farms secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Fredericksburg Farms uses the following methods for this purpose:
SSL Protocol
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
Children Under Thirteen
Fredericksburg Farms does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Fredericksburg Farms by contacting us here.
Changes to this Statement
Fredericksburg Farms will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Fredericksburg Farms encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Fredericksburg Farms is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Fredericksburg Farms welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Fredericksburg Farms has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Fredericksburg Farms at:
Fredericksburg Farms 8318 Ranch Road 1376 Fredericksburg, Texas 78624Contact Us Telephone number: (830) 997-0960
Effective as of June 1, 2019
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
